{
  "answers" : {
    "0" : {
      "author" : "persopn asd",
      "content" : "this is a content",
      "question" : "0"
    },
    "1" : {
      "author" : "persopn asd",
      "content" : "this is another content",
      "question" : "0"
    },
    "2" : {
      "author" : "asdasd jlh",
      "content" : "this is a thirs content",
      "question" : "0"
    },
    "3" : {
      "author" : "dasdasd",
      "content" : "sadasdas",
      "question" : "1"
    },
    "4" : {
      "author" : "persopn asd",
      "content" : "this is a content",
      "question" : "2"
    },
    "5" : {
      "author" : "persopn asd",
      "content" : "this is a content",
      "question" : "2"
    },
    "-KKVjypjDFJeV38pPGFY" : {
      "author" : "asdasd",
      "content" : "sadasdasd",
      "question" : "1"
    },
    "-KKVk-LzGZbW0RAkHzR3" : {
      "author" : "oh lord",
      "content" : "dave",
      "parentAnswer" : "-KKVjypjDFJeV38pPGFY",
      "question" : "1"
    },
    "-KKVph1Yst25DXaAlq8t" : {
      "author" : "dasdas",
      "content" : "sadsadsadas",
      "parentAnswer" : "-KKVjypjDFJeV38pPGFY",
      "question" : "1"
    },
    "-KKVqZvW0FamyxKGM-RC" : {
      "author" : "sadsadas",
      "content" : "sadsad",
      "question" : "1"
    },
    "-KKVr5QoVvDNVV34H7nS" : {
      "author" : "too cool",
      "content" : "whatever",
      "parentAnswer" : "1",
      "question" : "0"
    },
    "-KKVrePJaCw2sx9P9jsH" : {
      "author" : "sadasd",
      "content" : "fdsasddsad",
      "parentAnswer" : "3",
      "question" : "1"
    },
    "-KKVrpzwN4ISohxrVnoK" : {
      "author" : "xzcxzc",
      "content" : "xzxzzxzxzxczx",
      "parentAnswer" : "2",
      "question" : "0"
    },
    "-KKVs7z6a43TeT3AOKZV" : {
      "author" : "cxzcxzc",
      "content" : "xzcxzcxzzxc",
      "parentAnswer" : "0",
      "question" : "0"
    },
    "-KKVsKGCgvPirepj-5fU" : {
      "author" : "mr.cat",
      "content" : "hello mr. dog\n",
      "parentAnswer" : "4",
      "question" : "2"
    }
  },
  "questions" : [ {
    "answers" : {
      "0" : true,
      "1" : true,
      "2" : true,
      "-KKVr5QoVvDNVV34H7nS" : true,
      "-KKVrpzwN4ISohxrVnoK" : true,
      "-KKVs7z6a43TeT3AOKZV" : true
    },
    "author" : "persopn asd",
    "content" : "this is a content",
    "date" : 0,
    "notes" : "kljasd alskdjasldkjnsan alks jdnalksjd;ihf; sfh ;osdliusdfh lknz lkjdfnldzfkljkl zdlfk jzfdklj dfkj nzliudf n zdlkj n zdflk jzdklfjzdskfjn zdsklj zdsfkljn zfsdflkjfzlkjn kzsdflzkj"
  }, {
    "answers" : {
      "3" : true,
      "-KKVjypjDFJeV38pPGFY" : true,
      "-KKVk-LzGZbW0RAkHzR3" : true,
      "-KKVph1Yst25DXaAlq8t" : true,
      "-KKVqZvW0FamyxKGM-RC" : true,
      "-KKVrePJaCw2sx9P9jsH" : true
    },
    "author" : "persopn asd",
    "content" : "this is another content",
    "notes" : "Jhdhdhdshd kljasd alskdjasldkjnsan alks jdnalksjd;ihf; sfh ;osdliusdfh lknz lkjdfnldzfkljkl",
    "points" : 0
  }, {
    "answers" : {
      "4" : true,
      "5" : true,
      "-KKVsKGCgvPirepj-5fU" : true
    },
    "author" : "asdasd jlh",
    "content" : "this is a thirs content",
    "notes" : "kljasd alskdjasldkjnsan alks jdnalksjd;ihf; sfh ;osdliusdfh lknz lkjdfnldzfkljkl zdlfk jzfdklj dfkj nzliudf n zdlkj n zdflk jzdklfjzdskfjn zdsklj zdsfkljn zfsdflkjfzlkjn kzsdflzkjkljasd alskdjasldkjnsan alks jdnalksjd;ihf; sfh ;osdliusdfh lknz lkjdfnldzfkljkl zdlfk jzfdklj dfkj nzliudf n zdlkj n zdflk jzdklfjzdskfjn zdsklj zdsfkljn zfsdflkjfzlkjn kzsdflzkjkljasd alskdjasldkjnsan alks jdnalksjd;ihf; sfh ;osdliusdfh lknz lkjdfnldzfkljkl zdlfk jzfdklj dfkj nzliudf n zdlkj n zdflk jzdklfjzdskfjn zdsklj zdsfkljn zfsdflkjfzlkjn kzsdflzkj",
    "points" : 0
  } ]
}
